My heart is going crazy
I’m crazy
1 2 3 Let’s go
너를 볼 때면 난 계속
Whenever I look at you,
Smile spreads all over my face
입가에 미소가 막 번지게 돼
Please let me breathe
부디 날 숨 좀 쉬게 해줘
Please don’t make me a fool
You give me butterflies
날 떨리게 해
Everything I see is pitch dark,
눈앞이 전부 캄캄해
Please light it up, just like that
불을 밝혀줘 Just like that
Only for me, give me give your love
나에게만 Give me give your love
All day long, my thoughts are filled with you,
온종일 나의 생각 속엔
Just like this
너로 가득 차 Just like this
Hey, can you hear my heartbeat?
My heart is like BOOM BA RA BI BOMB BOMB
Throwing my heart at you
Watch out KABOOM BOOM BOOM
You’re my love I’m falling
Eye to eye just feel me now
I want you baby
Ooh you make me crazy now
My heart is like BOOM BA RA BI BOMB BOMB
Throwing my heart at you
Watch out KABOOM BOOM BOOM
You’re my love I’m falling
Eye to eye just feel me now
I want you baby
Oh I’m running to you baby
Want you to love me tonight
The moment this night lights up
이 밤이 밝혀진 순간
바라봐 줘 내 눈만
Please look at my eyes only
Your radiance keeps lighting a fire in my heart
빛이 나는 네가 내 맘에 자꾸 불을 붙여
Help me now
Whenever I look at you,
난 항상 너를 보면
My heart goes pit a pat
빨라지는 심장의 속도
몸이 너에게 반응하네
My body reacts to you,
Gotta gotta spark the fire we lit KABOOM
Everything I see is pitch dark,
눈앞이 전부 캄캄해
Please light it up, just like that
불을 밝혀줘 Just like that
Only for me, give me give your love
나에게만 Give me give your love
All day long, my thoughts are filled with you,
온종일 나의 생각 속엔
Just like this
너로 가득 차 Just like this
Hey, can you hear my heartbeat?
My heart is like BOOM BA RA BI BOMB BOMB
Throwing my heart at you
Watch out KABOOM BOOM BOOM
You’re my love I’m falling
Eye to eye just feel me now
I want you baby
Ooh you make me crazy now
My heart is like BOOM BA RA BI BOMB BOMB
Throwing my heart at you
Watch out KABOOM BOOM BOOM
You’re my love I’m falling
Eye to eye just feel me now
I want you baby
Oh I’m running to you baby
Want you to love me tonight
I wanna know what you do
No matter how hard I try, I can’t figure it out
아무리 애를 써도 알 수 없네
My complicated emotions,
복잡한 내 마음들도
With my sincere heart
솔직한 마음으로
I’m going to explode me toward you
널 향해 나를 터트린다
My heart is like BOOM BA RA BI BOMB BOMB
(OK just love me like that)
Watch out KABOOM BOOM BOOM
Eye to eye just feel me now
I want you baby
Ooh you make me crazy now
My heart is like BOOM BA RA BI BOMB BOMB
(OK just love me like that)
Watch out KABOOM BOOM BOOM
Eye to eye just feel me now
I want you baby
Oh I’m running to you baby
Want you to love me tonight